妈
妈妈
a pile of oregons without the spark of self from a brain
or the pump of blood from a heart
just to put you straight for a Sunday lunch now
who would like to reconstruct the audience
and who can tell human from animal
if there is a difference
come come you did puzzles as children did you not so just me
or is it definishly hard to concentrate
when the monsters talking
he's an extraordinary surgeon
his research is groundbreaking
his father found it this place are you mistaking
yourself as included in this conversation max metanicals
physical proximity to us does not make it so fuck up bulpa
give us a suit
you really think that's where the liberals are can
i ask what is the purpose of putting them back
in i
am
Mr max mccandles walk with me at the end of the lesson
your peer mind
you liked it sir
it showed signs of a conventional mind explaining
hard to almost touch mediocrity thank you
i need someone i'm a sister
honor portrict i would love to
and you're a religious man
i believe in god
me or the deity
humorous i see as you often know it is a joke of my own
making i do not need an explicator for me daddy's work
and he's also grown a beer and look like a big dog in a cravat
kids like dogs this
job
yes come on
hello evil Bella
this is mister mccandles
hello Bella
no ah bird blood blood blood blood
yes i'm i'm fine i'm fine
was a very pretty retard
she suffered her brain injury
i repair it
her mental age and her body are not quite synchronized
language is coming
she's progressing at an accelerated piece
she is dying
i need to meticulously note progression
you will do this for me
it will be my honor please
please
yes
it is exciting Bella
we are unleashes your message
friend
为
do you know like kippers
i am quite Washington
actually i finally be uh nice and in the morning
belllicop two just dead ones for Bella
just dead just dead
嘿嘿嘿
跳跳
she she gathers fifteen words a day
coordination is unstable at best
in the evening is this progress
her hair grows one inch
every two days
our hair does gonna be excellent you may go see you tomorrow
so where did she come from
i believe your job is collecting data
when i add any questions to it
i'll let you know
啊啊
哈哈哈哈
oh
yeah
and so when they returned from the wood
she was reunited with her mommy and daddy that night for dinner
they eat cake until they were sick
they were so happy to be back together
you need daddy card
i promise
you not be Bella nova girl
would i be nowhere
you are an orphan your parents died
then you cut parents up god
no
they were my friends they were brave explorers
they were killed in a landslide in South America
they pushed the boundaries of what was known
and they paid the price but that is the only way to live there
they sent you to me to care for you
dead
i'm afraid for my darling
poor better
i love god
good night
dear Bella
this parents
Peru
yes
why you pen book every nut
i must note down your nutritional
indate
how long
tell about other places
that's Lisbon Portugal
the south of France
the Alps
Australia far away
and dangerous in both people and animals
hello one look good world
Bella i don't think we're loud up here
来了
Bella this is dangerous
god
outside must go outside
no we work cut fingers candles
take me candle of
of course
i can it all yes out
has you ever been outside no
i have created a perfectly entertaining and safe world for them
now
you know
so many things outside
can kill your mother
they're dead snakes carriages
sharp face birds
earthquakes inhalation of toxic grass seeds
来了
now
look
why are funny thumbs god
once when i was very small
my father pinned
my thumbs into a small iron case to see whether
he could return the gross cycle of
bones now the pain was so great to stop myself from weeping
i would stare deeply into my other fingers
and simply by observation
begin to pass out the epidemiological elements
when he came back to his surprise
i was smiling
good god he was a man of unconventional mind
a time to go
a storm approaches
promise you scare herself
she's an experiment
and i must control the conditions
or our results will not be pure
huh stop gobby
go
no Bella belly want walking ice cream no fella once my face
people scared of god laugh at god
god lovely loved dog face
woof
woof great stop me Woof talk
no now no never just no
啊
啊啊啊啊啊
啊啊啊啊
啊
啊啊
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
i'm sorry my darling
mother of god
what did you do to her
why are you hiding her
tell me what all this means
or i'll go to the police
i shout for it is a happy day
it is rare to get a body or be a dead
but so close to life rigger had not set in the body
had hardly could no repulse
but some electric current so i could have kept her life
but she intended
i knew nothing of the life she had abandoned except she hated it
so much that she had chosen not to be
and forever what would she feel on being dragged from her
carefully chosen like eternity and
forced to be put in one of our understaffed poorly equipped
manhouse's reformed tracer jays for in this Christian nation
suicide is treated as lunacy
a crime who was i to decide her fate
but then there was also on my part of recognition
all my research had come to this moment fate
had brought me a dead body and a life infant it was obvious
it was take the infant's brain out and put it in the food row
woman reanimate her and watch Jesus
she knows no was she no idea
but would you rather the world
did not have better
Mrs brook belly discover happy when she wants hmm
you are a sour face
but i fixed you
her does
oh
no just wait it takes a moment
she grabbed my hairy business she's sick
Bella
Bella have discovered something
i must share what what we want
no
Bella huh Bella cease working yourself immediately
why in polite society that is not done uh
uh do not
what is that
my father took out
my Austin taking paloric glance
so i must make my own gust of Jesus
why god's name would he do that to discover
what no one knew turns out
we need them ideally
baba
you have not eaten
do not
good night
哇哇
you know i'm actually something of a romantic max
what i believe i see love between you and Bella
i she's perhaps you should marry her what i think she loves you
i've seen people look at each other
with loveness and observant subject
of course i see it you do
i i am i do have feelings for so you could take better out
better um i
feel funny
i was wondering if perhaps
you were raising her to be your mistress a dark thought
unworthy of me i know
so you were not playing with her
spinatic ejaculation can only induce homeostasis in me
if accompanied by prolonged stimulation of higher nerve seconds
whose pressure on the doctor's glance changes
the chemistry of my blood not for a few spasmoded minutes
but for many days
but i am unit
and that fuck off to get a sexual response for my body
would take the same amount of electricity as roms
north London besides my fraternal feelings seem to obey
my sexual thoughts
i apologize for my own
thoughtful not back at all meant
indeed all sexuality is basically immortal
not all sir do you wish to marry her or not
i wish to marry you be my wife
let's just touch each other's genital pieces uh
no no
i do not wish to take advantage of you you were special
when we are wet
one condition she must desire also
i understand the two conditions then that when you said
and you must live here with me always
have another legal agreement drawn up
curious
contract there are several
spelling errors and immaterial to legal binding is very shy of
must be quite a woman to warrant such binding
if you excuse me
do you use a facility
are you five years old
that you can't hold your water
weak plan sir like my father before me and his beforehead
you may have frosted cancer look into it will do
spend the bags that per your contract no doubt
afternoon visiting man what my hat would it suit me
yes ha
ha it is a foolish cash
i had to meet this woman who would inspire
such a contractive marriage of who prisons her
what do you mean
we should live here
travel with Mr Max mccandles and bags to abroad
not go forth in the city i see
they love me tight
i understand why i have to pinch you or see
if you're real you mountain
who is you
mister Duncan
letterburn
how you get up here
you watch me off no more
you did not see me working on myself to get happiness
did you this is not the light
i know
do not care for polite society
it's fucking boring destroys one's soul
god not believe in soul
i think god's the actual author of the soul idea godwin Baxter
a bad dog what is that story
you're a prisoner right aim to free you
something in you some hungry being hungry for experience freedom
touch see the unknown and know it so why am i here
you ask i'm going to Lisbon on Friday
i'd like you to come Lisbon of Portugal that is the Lisbon
i speak of
of never in ours
so i'm not asking you
i'm asking you
better not safe with you i think you are absolutely not
now have a moment to value time dear god
of course
Barack
i wanted to tell you big news belly is dizzy but excited
what is it tonight at midnight
i secretly run away with one dunken wedding
butt what you will wish to stop me
i say stop you
you hold
Bella tootight i must set forth into waters we can travel you
me and max whom
i will remind you
you are betrayed to i will marry max
as he seems right for that
but first i shall adventure on Duncan weddeber who
i think has little damaged me
but will be interesting as well
i can't help you go
kiss me and set me forth
if you do not
but as insides should turn rotten with hate hate hate
unpack those bags of prim godwin has told me your plan
i do not blame you Bella
that man is a cat and a rake
he is insidious ways of getting under a naive woman's skin
it is mostly his eyes on mine
and his hands were between bella's legs and whispered words
i can't hear
but heat in my
body Jesus Bella we are engaged
i love you when i return
we marriage be happy
as two doves on the branch you think i need travel hat no
this will not do it cannot up see to this man myself
i will beat his handsome face into a porridge of blood
and bones max
you are flushed and i am too at sight of different max
i apologize
but i will not let a man that i know has nothing
but intense in his mind and nothing for you in his heart
trip you i will smash his fucking headed
goodbye later dove i will see you after grand adventure
go
she's gone
i'm having pot the breakfast is strangely delicious
why did you not stop her
she is a being a free will
she's now out there alone
she will be fine i'm a fool
i should have stopped her we are a man of science
this emotionality is unseenly
just hope she's all right
you're the most beautiful woman i've ever seen
we're not lie i've been with many Missus
Prim said you were wolf who sent a hundred women on you
she understands it okay wasters have you had them before
i have not
shop shopping bubble
嗯
rolling
so nuns and monks
and starves their clothes
as the egg whites and the yolks make these tops now
how to eat them
i will get through
the mouth they must not be eating dainty flake by dainty flake
but in here there's guster like life itself
incredible who made this way more
no more learns enough
animals too much it's yester time what is yester
why do people not just do this
all the time
well
at the risk of being immodest
you've just spent thrice funds by the very best
it's probably not the man that will bring you to the raptures
i have
i feel bad for you
because it will just be you are
you furious jumping with furious jumping
i love that i'm rested
let's just go again again unfortunately
even i have my limits men cannot keep coming back for more
it is a physiological problem a weakness in men
hmm well
perhaps
so
you be advised if it's not too late
not to fall in love with me
i have very little often way of constancy just adventure i see
let us sleep
thanks madam
feelings to something
yes will be there with you
we feel the truth something
he has to be mine
unless you're going to
no one's you
good evening
drunken wedderburn bellan where were you disappeared i did not
hope you can just disappear what family disappear
no of course what the fuck are you talking about
where were you
i wanted to attack and then an adventure fell
i did not know how to return
and then i heard it the trap
i will move to the noise and i found it amazement to Bella
explore blood in me
Bella it's dangerous to go out without me
i have adventured it and found nothing
but sugar and violence it is most charming i am fine now
i must lie down
and you must lie down on top of me and do more furious jumping
did you see the new show in London
by wow
marvelously witty
i loved it a handbag
bell
what
why keep it in my mouth
if it is revolting
i've said that before to Gerald hahaha
thank you catch my drink
you are wicked
oh because you mean his penis
duncans can sometimes be salty
i must go punch that baby
your behavior is uncautionable
we behave the food was packing my thread
the baby annoying and the woman boring with birds
you will rejoin the table
you can find yourself to the following three phrases
how marvelous delighted
and how did they make pastry so crisp
yes
you are hurting that love
sorry
reason does not penetrate but let's go
are you enjoying
Lisbon
Bella
delighted
jj
how would you dear father
it's very unwell
i fear he will not see the year out how how marvelous
how did they get the pastry soap crisp
good god
what is it
from her
me good Lisbon sugar top lick me all day
at least
i hope that's all on sentence anyway
do you think that plugging
yes
also relating the tram
哈哈哈哈
耶
your headache too Johnson
went to burn and i also am starving for dinner
where the fuck are you
Victoria Blessington
i haven't seen you for years and you still
have not as i am Bella Baxter
strange feathered lady
i apologize i could have sworned you
a sheen
right
shall we
the steak the fish
the little caramel things and pots that all spots of people over
there
have no no more kind of no than fox
of course
not i was all for Bella
all right your whim no cross of Bella's outings and adventures
and yet we must discover
by will as spoken by Duncan Weddeburn to Bella Baxter day
one of his Belovapha
share understand we never lived outside god's house
so Bella
so much to discover and your sad face makes me discover
angry feelings for you
right
become the very thing i hate grasping succuleus for a lover
five many of them off me now i'm it
you like me and a creature of fever and mountains
what did you do that for the man
after repeats blinks
today
i blink back for tonight i've been
we're going to them
i have never done this in town
you're quite mad stop talking as your sounds make Bella angry
not stop talking by yourself to the sound
a man was teaching me chess
and he said he thought i would probably have the softest skin
he had ever touched
when i said if i did it would be the inner thighs to test
as that is where the epidermis is at its most fine so he tested
and it was the softest to ever
i wondered if perhaps they not equal in soltitude indeed
they were not so i made sure to note it remembering which was
which
what
if the tongue play you were about to perform
is that not happening
you are troubled
did he lie with you
no we were against the war
did you furious jump him
no he just passed looked by clitoris
i had the heat they needed release so in my request it was
you two may tongue play me
so not understanding this complicated feeling
are you now crying
what a confusing person
you are uncle winterburn
a liver
a small incision is all that is needed
i was plotted from codes one morning
i may have ingested
too much
i am going to venture to suggest
you are upset by bella's absence that needs a support sobbing
are here at night
good dark man
you fighting like an imbecile she is gone
i am a man of science
i just need to engage in and continue the project that is all
i must go on to
the next thing
our feelings must be put aside
do you think my father could have branded me
with hot irons of the genitals
the way
he did if he could not put science in progress first brand
let us find a body
a what
hello
good morning
good morning John
i haven't been very supportive of your adventure spirit
so i'm surprised for you
get it
we changed hotels
because the window been
we are on both indeed
you aim to trap better and see
i aim to give you a new adventure suppose it's true
you'll be easier to find come just roll me ride me
no then have cocktails on fordeck
shit on me
madam
when do we stop three days
the woman on fire no
i know you're upset with me
forgive my kidnapping of your books for love a romantic chair
don't be such a cunt about it
i want a drink of course
my darling this is fun whole world to explore
do you love me i love you
describe the elements
i should be looking for within myself to be sure
you just feel a lot
so there's no evidence space as god would say
so how dodge
it impare with me
what the fuck are you talking about
who are who are you
you don't know what bananas
are you never heard of chess and yet you know what imperating me
Bella wants a drink said twice now
i've never felt anything like this is this true for you
i suppose empirically is
i'm out of the ink
then ink you share my love
no interesting old lady i must touch your hair
i also noticed your hair just like silk on a translucent glowing
egg at his fancy ones that excite me
somehow i saw you with handsome over there
white teeth and a hardcuff
Duncan went to burn his teeth are also hard
his penis is also white good layeval
he is my only
but i find him to elicit
exceptional sensation
throughout my whole body that leave me yelping happily
i also wish to dash
his body form
cadaver into the sea is this man jumping on your body no
he is not i have been buried in twenty years
what that is terrible it doesn't concern
me greatly as years have passed what's in between my ears
is my big concern
what's in between my legs
much less sort desperate rationalization Martha oh
this is Harry Ashley don't take what
he says too much
too hard
here's a cynic madam
i am Bella Baxter i do not know what this cynic is Bella
Inc
Duncan waiter burn i have made friends colleagues comrades
Harry Astley
this is Malta
she is my new friend
who has not been fucked in twenty years
and that not astonishment
i hope you use your hand
between your legs to keep yourself happy
good god Bella
you cannot speak like this polite society
forgot
polite society will destroy you
it will there
there isn't truth enough
we all agreed on that as the inquiry on my hand occasionally
yes
that is what reassuring you is
we shall all dine together
right
actually
we are all on a ship and cannot escape
and there is a world to enjoy traverse
circumnavigate
or can she not have friends
mister weddebra hmm delighted
Mary me
what i meant to throw
you aside a few months and send you packing
but i cannot say oh
Mary me
no one's ever captured my heart you have
it is tricky as i am engaged to Mr matts with candles
what my hand has taken by another it is a saying i heard
but did not understand you do not take just the hand at all
do you not
you ran away with me
from him
accounting of events the point of
which is elusive to me you chose me over him for now for fun
i'll fucking throw you overboard
so you wish to marry me or kill me
is that the proposal
no
that's fine
she is coming along
let's try again gross mortar skills will develop slowly
but you will progress fast
publicity
i'm reading Emerson speaks about the improvement men
i do not know why he does not give advice to women perhaps
he does not know any
dry and read good philosophy is a
waste of time
Bella really say more no
no harry
you're wretched
it is a dagger people and society can be improved
it is the goal of all to prove advance progress grow
i know this in me
and i'm sure i am indicative of all but trust me
you're definitely unique fella in always
but this improvement
through philosophy
is people trying to run away from the fact that we are all
cruel beasts born that way die that way
it is a dark view of things harry better
let us take the air
in our cabin
these two are fighting ideas of banging around in bella's head
and heart like lights in the storm
oh
you're always reading now
Bella
you're losing some of your adorable way of speaking
i'm a changingable feast as a rule of weak apparently
according to Emerson disagreed with by Harry come come just come
you were in my son
what
come
busy drinking heavily
busy losing heavily
must go be Martha
Martha
she is the problem after that perfume bag of flesh up
i dare you
where are you going
she's going over the side
all marvelous
i never imagined being murdered how dramatic well
she seems happy to die i'm sorry for giving your life
i'll be on the ball
you have made me think cogitate harangulate on ideas
that are wrong erroneous
and nonsensically annoying that leave me not to sleep
so
you say all a cruel and i disagree is a vow and say you're not
but when with Duncan
the cruel just bubbles up in me
that shows good judgment he is a pretty moron
no
i do not wish to be cruel i must improve this aspect myself
you don't know the world and you fear it
i do not do it do you want to see what
the world is really like
i'll show you yes
of course
you hear that
what is it
lot of dead babies uh must be hot
we must go help them how will we do that
we go down there
though quite right we rope us
rob us and rape us
and if they were here and we were there
we do the same to them
we are casting off mom
but i have to go back
i i must give this money to the poor near the hotel
in what they call a son
we're staying a show mom
we could take care of that for you you can
of course it is generous of you they need money everyone does
thank you
you deep in the captain that will find this fucking thief better
we've been robbed i i want i want everything like never before
and now it's now it's gone
not been robbed i took it
what i took it
i'm so tired
maybe just my spirit is my soul has buckled crumpled flattened
drunken wetterburg by the sights i have seen
so no need for the calculator fuck off before i break
all your peep
no need sir
where is it
you hid it for safety
i was drunk a foolish lifted everywhere whatever
i did not hide it i gave it to those poor people out there
money is its own form of sickness and all the scarcity of it
and who am
i lying for the bed
what dead babies liar did you
doctor
do what
i am expecting a hug of solace you
i need to offer something to the world yet
i have nothing except some money
it is a bad day for better Baxter
where is my fucking money
i just told you i gave it away to the poor
i thought i told you to fuck off
the studio informs
me that
you may not have sufficient funds to make good your account
sir well
that's probably true
i gave it all to some nice men to pass on to the sun poor
you'll be put
ashore at the next port
and confined to prove Russians until then so good evening
how dare you
dead mind babies bit harry
my love was full of blood
she is a rhythm
how's your hand
it's fine i'm sorry
you're trying to help me understand no
i actually wanted to hurt
you couldn't bear to see such dumb beautiful
happiness in someone it was cruel of me
i am not
sorry
if i know the world
i can prove it you can't that is the real point
don't accept the live religion
socialism capitalism
we are a fuck species know it hope is smashable
realism is not protect yourself with the truth
i realize what you are now
harry
just a broken little boy
who cannot bear the pain of the world
i suppose so
goodbye harry
we get thrown off in Marseille why do you stay with him
i always think it will be better of
course you do
i've had great things of beauty of Paris
fucking kicks your dog to death
fucking passion no money what do you suggest we do
Bella
i was in this hotel not worry
uh huh
what we have no money
is it not an interesting experiment with nothing
how will we live now
i don't know exactly
that's the experiment we are now
the pool also
many adventurers have faced these odds
Robertson cruiser for example
selfish softless
careless bitch
i'm not faultless Duncan more
it is true my ability to think things
through to the logical conclusion is not strong
i did help those suffering people i have ruined us
as you pointed out
but i do believe my actions come from a good place
shut the fuck up
i will go to the hotel
good afternoon madam for that thing
my fresh starling English rose is this a hotel
we have rooms are you looking for look how much
is the room
i charge you ten francs an hour you charge them
thirty everyone's happy
i see
i'm sister fell fresh from London Pondigoon what's your day
hello
what's what affair
so figure at this point
i am confused you're not here to work
but come on lie with him
let him cock you a bit
make some nice ranks i see he would pay me for this yes
if you need money
it is the shortest route to it
i've never been cocked by another man
yet i've wandered on that
and i'm in need of funds
it is i believe a confluence of circumstances i regard
is almost fate
like let us do this
room sixteen
怎么说
what is your name
should we warm me up a bit
good day sir
the Clara shock
a laugh
i've come to some money and some enlightenment you still
you've always said
you're the best badman in the world
and i've never known another
so knew not whether this is true
but now i do
and he was terrible and made unbodly noises
as he thrust himself into me
and a mere three thrust
Duncan went burn was only commanded first
i laugh but polite of course
i took his money
i thanked him i lost all the way to buy his busy players
but so fondly remembering the best sweaty nights of us
fuck for money and as an experiment
which is good for our relationship is it gladdens
my heart told you
my heart has been a bit dim on your weedy squaring
person lately
you are a monster
a horror monster
a demon sent from hell to rip my spirit
defense to punish my tiny
sins with a tsunami of destruction to take my heart
and put in my topic to ruin me
i look at you when i see nothing
but happiness at last
it was uncalled for it makes no sense
as your odes to my beauty have been boring
but constant and the simple act of letting a strange man
ride on me has erased all that
what you you hold yourself
you are now going to explain to me as bad
can i never win with you
it is the worst that woman can do
we should definitely never marry
i'm a flawed experimenting person
and i will need a husband or the more forgiving this position
can't i can now see
you are not that our adventure is clearly over
i shall book your passage back to London you had money
this whole time
it is god's money for emergencies
it has been a fucking emergency for weeks now
i believed in you
the whole time that you would rise to the occasion
but now i see that was a mistake
and there's clearly something broken in you
you propent something in me
i feel this conversation has become circular
Madam swine i had examined my situation i need sex and money
i could take a lover
another wedded burn
would keep me may require an awful lot of attention
or else it's twenty minutes at a time
and the rest of my days free study on the world
and the improvement of it
hence i seek employment that you must be smelling
establishment of good time fornication
a woman plotting her course to freedom and not all
i'm mister saver
i feel in you
a prime cart
Maxie a boo
Bella
say follow me down let the end house rolls
that smell you
啊哈哈
fold me down see
i'm a shrine and i want all of them this man
empty just because teasiness and super English
they see it was brutal in a strangely not
unpleasant way
bumphlet she's a sadist read what is
that it doesn't you will change the world for the mayor
make it better a better world
i'm mad too
madam swiney this lineup system
you really expect me to go upstairs with the man
even if i find him distasteful
and therefore
i'm sad when i let him curious jump me
that is the way it is i hardly
'cause you're the pretty how it agrees with you to be rapaged
suppose sir
no we feel we we miss master Bella
so would you not prefer it
if the women chose as it would be a sign of enthusiasm told you
you wouldn't have the vague sense that they're
in a state of horror
when you jump them
ah huh and that's all fine who's here
monsieur millso
Bella is new and may have a mental illness and the compost of
god my father
says
it is only the way it is until we discover the new way it is
and then that is
the way it is until we discover the new way it is
and so it goes until the world is no longer flat
electricity lights
the night and shoots no longer time with ribbons
Russian echo as a socially stable entire fondo tonight
you have
such a clever mouth monsieur meloso will enjoy it for free go
now Bella among them in my office
you have the most delicious looking lobes thank you Anna ah ah
ah
oh i am sorry i drew blunt yeah
but sometimes give in to myself a nicely beauty
young beauty for one day my dear
you will be a wrinkled old husk and now
i will want you either to pay for it
or to have it for free
i still believe everyone will be happier
if we could choose an idea like me
how delightful you are
but we must give in to the demands of the world
sometimes grapple with it try to defeat him
do you believe it's me
of course but some men enjoy that you do not like him what
i think that good business
probably
my grandchild seeking poorly and requiring much doctoring
my choice of giving you choice will jeopardize the business
her health her life do you want that Bella
of course not your tongue you're so low
i thought you going for my love hahaha
we must work
we must make money
but more than that we must experience everything
not just the good
but degradation horror sadness
this makes us whole better
most people of substance not flighty untouched children
then we can know the world
only know the world
the world is ours i want
but now go and fuck someone and bring me ten francs
first i suggest a short quiz
a quiz
you tell me a childhood memory soothing
the adomfon
then i tell a joke talk
talk
then a quick sniff and if necessary a quick
douse in lavender royal
and all of this will enhance the experience
making it form a doubt talk talk
talk talk
no i tell the joke you the memory resume
you're so young comes at the better of this is the sweet
don't buy the one below
you little in grease you fell from your bicycle way
superman say a machine hmm uh
three rapper must say i say a blunt them alone
there is one thing in the right times joy
you watched the blood with joy with knock
knock kiss her homage
homage key cheese to meet
you
smell okay at his park
god gave you a gift my friend
too many Dixon
this is what you do when you're homesick
you wish what my boys are often ask for education
sexual
i will demonstrate
i see hello
which way i guess i'm not fun so now i'm going beneath
it's accent
at times
she want to business the song of the park
which are business once man later
so Montgomery song
ya
this is all of your mouth
there two eight things along a finger in the old
or it's like choking
啊
啊啊啊
啊啊
啊
ah
ah Adam swiney was right
i am discovering part to myself here that you unknown
there's a way to limit
it variety of desires being made manifest is fascinating
if you have the man who puts a wedge pineapple in your
mouth and comes you in dust have you said crying
little spread up
Emma started to forgive you and booked our first home
and told mother to prepare our wedding
bed did you fuck that guy
look so hand you dear
no
i beat the tar on that guy
Duncan i thought you left back to the ship
it started aching bombing so i'm here to save you
you know
i don't care can't get this show me go
home Duncan
our time has ended
i look at you
and feel nothing for the lingering question of how did
i ever want you
oh
and we must go to the meeting of substionists
your horns
we are our own means of production go away
foot
eight
foot very good
language is slow
but improving eight foot genius can you not be so poor to her
i made a mistake with mala
allowed feelings to develop the long for her
she is no different to the chicken dog
but it is better this way perhaps
give some insight into my father's cruel system
it was a necessity of science good god
then i do not expect you to understand village doctor
by the way i need you to operate
shall i put a beating heart in your monstrous form
if you have time when taking
this sight
all the moves insists from around me to no need
you may close me up to spread
i see tiny polyps
i'm dying how
to break it to the patient day
do not cry into the world
you'll kill me faster with sepsis quiet now close me up
find her
i am close
hot
chocolate my dear and i'll sugar now
it one my favorite
i heard
you said that to the others
we are a machine you feed with compliments and chocolate
you are my children i feed with love
something terrible has happened
so i feel almost nothing
my empathy is creeping toward what
i would describe as contemptuous rage
it is fabulous
it is
you are in the dark period before light and wisdom come to you
you must forge through it
and once on the other side you will be grateful to this moment
but you must keep going i see
miss you
my tongue baby
my niece is malama rezam
i don't have one it is an accident scar
but you're not the first to have made the mistake
i lie
i'm not lying my godwin told me himself
good day sir
you wrote to Mister
goldwin Baxter
he is such a demon at large into the world of devil's rat
and a luring body that cannot be satiated in her mind
that picks people apart
Stitch by Stitch
like a bloodied and burned red door shadow of an elephant song
Bella
where is she who are you
i'm her fiance
sir
obviously things did not end well between you
did not
she destroyed
me hmm
we're all masters of our own ship
so there's that i do not like you or your words that golden vex
that you knew was such a home to me
trapping me
where is she would not whisper on my worst enemy
i should save you from her sir
ah
forgive my frustration just tell me it does not hurt
i had no insight she hollered me out my son
my bank account i am a barbie
shed everything
oh you'll say this
death death
i do not wish to be like this
force my habit
oh mercy the old ship
you kind thing kind fish this shit
please
i ask you as plenty as i can where is she
the horse back
Bob Ella
matts Roden you are ill i am not i am dying a subtle difference
but one might take seriously a substition
you are the sights in the good
one who cannot buy
empirical data says different
i missed you i now have to lie down
there's not all sunshine i bring
they also bring bdis and hard questions
i have a baby in me and if so where is it
they see
well technically you are your baby
and also i suppose you are your mother
and also neither no memories survives
no experiences survive what do you mean
i a mother and daughter
you knew and did not tell i did not see good
reason to
and went to coward they too
but then to that as well
i wanted to be with you
and i was not sure you would even understand
and that's the kind of makes one of prisoner to him and and i am
sorry
who is this
nicely you've introduced me then prince i like this
one though that's not none of this
another one
we miss you
monsters
bang
bang bang
it is hard to be in a position
where one wants to hit someone who is already in obvious pain
it is a conunctor for sure
would
you rather be erased by the flesh with a fish up in your nose
i will feel good for a second about for longers
i really had a fish
look at my nose you did
so i am your creation
has this the other
one neither of you are
that she wanders the halls with a hammer and a song
and that is not my doing and i read your cards and letters home
and watched you fearlessly create by a bachelor with one
but i am finding being alive fascinating
so i'll forgive you the act
but always hate the lies and trapping that followed understood
good to see you you too
i made confusion and brain dissonance aside i missed you
i arrived home when i smelled the famaldehyde
and i knew what is fixed
i will be a doctor
my surgery is yours
my father wants to
always carve with compassion he was a fucking idiot
but it's not that advice
it does not have long i know
you've not mentioned our betrothal
you were much younger
there is no bind i was mesmerized by you and backstage advantage
so you were mesmerized no more
i am still mesmerized
i've been a whole you understand hmm Cox for money inside me
you okay with that
does the horing thing challenge the desire for ownership
that men have when Devon became
much weed being swearing when he discovered my horing
i find myself nearly jealous of the men's time
with you rather than any moral aspersion against you
it is your body better Baxter
you will see you free
i generally charge thirty francs well
that seems low
do you believe people improvable max
i do just as a human body can be cured of illness
so can men and women be cured of aspect
will you marry me back to candice
i will
we will need less of your time in the future
but overall most agreeable
hmm
i will take that note and have you been checked for um disease
i have not
but i shall i'm enjoying this practical love we have
but i i assure you mine is also passionate you are adorable
you always were
god you are walking i have taken five milligrams of heroin
through the tools for pain confederments for energy cocaine
because i am actually
cocaine i've come here
to walk you down the island
i'm sorry by the powers vested in me by the church
i shall solemnize this union do you
hear Bella Baxter
take this man
as your husband
did we miss the part about anyone objecting to this
or has that been removed in some kind of foe
modernization of the catanism
hello Victoria
you look well
do you refer to me sir
the man doesn't normally introduce himself to his wife
but if i must delete he is the golden
and you don't know if he's in her power
or she in his his devil's work at hands look
they calls not as an old man of blood
he has cancer you fucking idiot
don't you don't play your eyes on me demon
as i was saying general Alfred blessington
you really do not know
when Mister Weddeberg put your photo in the paper
i remember when that old bird in the hotel
called the Victoria blessing kid
and i pieced this dial follicle fuck
best of a puzzle together
you are your dear ralphie
you left in the state of some mental abdomen
and mysterio of your pregnancy on the discovery of your absence
i felt disemboweled
i have disemboweled met on the field of battle
i always imagined a dull hollow robbing that is what he was like
is also stench
but that does not apply as a metaphor here
but here you are my darling
here you are god
i have been recollection of you
i am Bella Banster helpful
but perhaps you've hit your head
and these men clearly taken advantage of you please go
sir
you were my husband
your dear Ralph Bella
i'm sorry
actually i would like to go
what
you're the carriage
sir
yes
let's just go
let me go god
that's who you want to me
it is good to have you back
Victoria
serve tonight not getting along i feel an uprising
you remember David darling
Alison look who's back
you know me
tell me about myself
was i nice
嗯
eat
all your favorites kippers goose tongue champagne
i missed you
what was the root of the unhappiness
what drove her to leave off the bridge
you hated the baby you called it the monster
i see
i have noticed a lack of maternal instinct
and yet i'm happy to have you home
how do we meet at a ball
why do we blind each other
we share a love of good times
watch
Allison sue
hahahaha ah absent we'll have some cheese when you can
i love
cruelty
was not a kind person it seemed kind
you would never be so dope Victoria appalling idea
when the burn says you were a whore i suspect
i was i was in Paris
i tired of it fascinating
right
this kippers are strangely delicious vinegary or something
marriage is a constant child
some we've been to some we've been to us
i will try to forgive you for the pouring
your sexual hysteria was often out in half
and for the killing of our unborn child
in fact when i list the ways you wrote me
Jesus Christ himself would probably beat your headed with a bat
you're blessed with forgiving husband
i'm not wrong
dear ralphie as i do not know you well
you're in luck and i've had a lot of experience in the field
with Amnesia
either men
who wish to forget where they were or a mortar exploded nearby
ringing the Ukrainium
like a church bell i suggest
we stick close to the house for several months maybe a year
until you've made a full recovery
i will leave it my leisure
but i am flattered by your desire to trap me
you're not first
i will have to shoot you in the fucking head if you try to leave
die the front of the back of the head
the back as to be sure
you were leaving and i was not being rash
i have with you
so i'm a prisoner
this conversation has gone down an fortunate route i am sure
you will be as happy as you were before
as i was before when i threw myself from a bridge
i suspect you felt while looking for fish
why would you want to keep me here
as i do not wish to stay if one must drown
let it be in the river of love
they did
does that pheasant look strip to the bone
i was in misjudgment
sir
i apologize
dessert done
comes up easy like a bomb sitting
i think we'll do it an ever chant rocks that had my own
more precise device made
do you want just a little hold of your hands as well
they're holding the federal package
it will come on that way
this time we'll get it done
i should get to sedated to bring it to your surgery
this evening
Victoria darling
where are you
perfect timing martini
well or not
i would however
like to leave i found our time together interesting
but if i ascertained
why i jumped from a bridge
i wish to go see my near dead god adorable
i hear unfortunately my darling
my life is dedicated to the taking of territory you are mine
and that is the long and short
i'm not territory
the root of the problem is between your legs i will have a dog
and it will not distract and divert you anymore
see a man spends his life
wrangling his sexual compulsion
it's a curse and yet in some ways
his life's work a woman's life's work is children
i intend to rid you that infernal packet between your legs
and plot to see in you straight after
let me explain what has happened Victoria your wife
threw herself from a bridge
and died godwin maxter found her brought it to his
surgery he then removed the baby
removed brain from the baby transplanted it into my head
and reanimated me
i'll bring you the file it's actually quite fascinating however
i will keep my new life my lovely old glitterist
thank you who would call a carriage for me and talk and talk
and yet at some point there's nothing left but to pull a gun
just the way with willing
are you giving it
i'd rather you shop me in the fucking hunt
i will oblige if i have to
drink the drink dummy chloroform and gin
in some ways
it would be a relief to be rid of by questing self sit deeply
and that freedom is yours
Max
Matt we have to get him to surgery alive
we don't bleeding a lot you're fucking dead
Bella if he lives
i do not sense he is a man who will stop
well i won't want him bleed to death
but i agree you can do with improvement
i removed the bullet and stopped the bleeding good news
i am never happier than when i'm in here
father you're back
it was just a story of someone else
not bennefax then
all my life paper's eyes looked at me or a pity
and you
it's all very interesting
what is happening
rescue
natural exam is making me nervous
i've tested you many times you know
it no one knows an answer me better than you Connie self team
uneffective
ladies jin
please jin
we should get some water for the general